Becina's a Microsoft Dynamics partner.
We are people business and the way we
drive new revenue and grow our business
is kind of adding more talent.
>> [music]
>> The challenges we were facing before we
joined BC Talent was inconsistent
[music]
flow in new talent. We had to constantly
look for new ways and do all the
training ourselves. [music]
>> Using the Upskill program, we were able
to use our own onboarding system and
[music] reduce it because we could move
a huge part of that process onto the
Upskill program. Using the Upskill
program along with the Microsoft brand
makes it more attractive for the youth
[music] to send their applications in.
>> We see the benefit of training [music]
with external people that are not within
our own organization is that they bring
on new perspectives. Being able to
recruit young talent is [music]
immensely important for us.
>> When they come out of the BC Talent
program, they actually had a lot of
knowledge and [music] they are pretty
self-confident about working and
engaging with the customers we have.
>> There's really no barrier not to join
the BC Talent program.
>> It's a never-ending learning process.
[music]
There's a bunch of stuff that you can
dive into all the time. [music]
>> The program will teach you the technical
skills about Business Central and the
soft skills that you need to be a
consultant.
>> In this [music] community, we can lean
on each other whenever we need to.
>> I definitely felt that there was a lot
of support. I can text [music] a
colleague from from the US or from Asia
and get an answer in no time.
>> [music]
>> We have been able to onboard 14 people
so far directly from education and we
see very very nice results. So, we're
[music] definitely going to do this once
more.
>> In the past, we've been used to just
having one or two people coming in and
we had to decide whether or not we
wanted to hire them. Suddenly, having
the luxury of picking [music] between
150 qualified people has been kind of
mind-blowing for us.
>> [music]